<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>  
  <chapter xml:id="overview">
    <title>Test Overview</title>
    <para xml:id="overview.para.1">
      This section provides information for the test setup procedure and required
      prerequisites that should be followed during test case execution.
    </para>
    <para xml:id="overview.para.3">
      An ONVIF Profile is described by a fixed set of functionalities through a number of
      services that are provided by the ONVIF standard. A number of services and
      functionalities are mandatory for each type of ONVIF Profile. An ONVIF Device and ONVIF
      Client may support any combination of Profiles and other optional services and
      functionalities.
    </para>
    <section xml:id="overview.general">
      <title>General</title>
      <para>
        Test Cases are grouped depending on features. Each Test Cases group provides description of feature requirement level for Profiles, expected scenario under test and related test cases:
        <itemizedlist>
          <listitem>
            <para>Feature Level Requirement</para>
          </listitem>
          <listitem>
            <para>Expected Scenarios Under Test</para>
          </listitem>
          <listitem>
            <para>List of Test Cases</para>
          </listitem>
        </itemizedlist>
      </para>
      <section xml:id="overview.general.feature_level_requirement">
        <title>Feature Level Requirement</title>
        <para>Feature Level Requirement item contains a feature ID, check condition based on Device features, required number of Devices and feature requirement level for the Profiles, which will be used for Profiles conformance.</para>
        <para>
          To claim this Feature as supported Client shall pass Expected Scenario Under Test:
          <itemizedlist>
            <listitem>
              <para>for each Device, which supports Device Features defined in Check Condition Based on Device Features</para>
            </listitem>
            <listitem>
              <para>for at least with number of Devices specified in Required Number of Devices</para>
            </listitem>
          </itemizedlist>
        </para>
        <para>If Feature Level Requirement is defined as Mandatory for some Profile, Client shall support this Feature to claim this Profile Conformance.</para>
      </section>
      <section xml:id="overview.general.expected_scenarios_under_test">
        <title>Expected Scenarios Under Test</title>
        <para>Expected Scenarios Under Test item contains expected scenario under test, conditions when the feature will be defined as supported and as not supported.</para>
      </section>
      <section xml:id="overview.general.test_cases">
        <title>Test Cases</title>
        <para>Test Case items contain list of test cases which are related to feature. Test cases provide exact procedure of testing feature support conditions.</para>
        <para>Each Test Case contains the following parts:</para>
        <itemizedlist>
          <listitem>
            <para>Test Label - Unique label for each test</para>
          </listitem>
          <listitem>
            <para>Test Case ID - Unique ID for each test</para>
          </listitem>
          <listitem>
            <para>Profile Normative References - Requirement level for the feature under test is defined in Profile Specification. This reference is informative and will not be used in conformance procedure.</para>
          </listitem>
          <listitem>
            <para>Feature Under Test - Feature which is under current test. Typically a particular command or an event.</para>
          </listitem>
          <listitem>
            <para>Test Purpose - The purpose of current test case.</para>
          </listitem>
          <listitem>
            <para>Pre-Requisite - The pre-requisite defines when the test should be performed. In case if pre-reqiusite does not match, the test result will be NOT DETECTED.</para>
          </listitem>
          <listitem>
            <para>Test Procedure - scenario expected to be reflected in network trace file.</para>
          </listitem>
          <listitem>
            <para>Test Result - Passed and failed criteria of the test case. Depending on these criteria test result will be defined as PASSED or FAILED.</para>
          </listitem>

        </itemizedlist>
      </section>
    </section>
    <section xml:id="overview.test_setup">
      <title>Test Setup</title>
      <para xml:id="overview.test_setup.para.1">Collect Network traces files required by the test cases.</para>
      <para xml:id="overview.test_setup.para.2">
        Collect Feature List XML files for Devices detected in the Network Trace
        files.
      </para>
      <para xml:id="overview.test_setup.para.3">
        Client shall support all mandatory and conditional features listed in the Device
        Feature List XML file supplied for the Profiles supported by the Client.
      </para>
    </section>
    <section xml:id="overview.prerequisites">
      <title>Prerequisites</title>
      <para>
        The pre-requisites for executing the test cases described in this Test
        Specification include:
      </para>
      <para>The Device shall be configured with an IPv4 address.</para>
      <para>The Device shall be able to be discovered by the Client.</para>
    </section>
  </chapter>